console.log("Hello, world!");

/** QUESTIONS */

let questions = [
    { 
        question: "What year was the UFC founded?",
        optionA: "1990",
        optionB: "1993",
        optionC: "1997",
        optionD: "2001",
        correct: "B"
    },     { 
        question: "Where was the first UFC event held?",
        optionA: "Denver, Colorado",
        optionB: "Las Vegas, Nevada",
        optionC: "Miami, Florida",
        optionD: "Toronto, Ontario",
        correct: "A"
    },     { 
        question: "Who was the first eve UFC champion?",
        optionA: "Royce Gracie",
        optionB: "Mark Coleman",
        optionC: "Anderson Silva",
        optionD: "Ken Shamrock",
        correct: "A"
    },     { 
        question: "Which fighter has the most successful UFC title defences?",
        optionA: "Conor McGregor",
        optionB: "Georges St Pierre",
        optionC: "Anderson Silva",
        optionD: "Israel Adesanya",
        correct: "C"
    },     { 
        question: "Who was the first female fighter to be induced into the UFC hall of fame?",
        optionA: "Holly Holm",
        optionB: "Amanda Nunes",
        optionC: "Joanna Jedrzejczyk",
        optionD: "Ronda Rousey",
        correct: "D"
    },     { 
        question: "Who holds the record for fastest knockout in UFC history?",
        optionA: "Jorge Masvidal",
        optionB: "Duane Ludwig",
        optionC: "Todd Duffee",
        optionD: "Chan Sung Jung",
        correct: "A"
    },     { 
        question: "What year was the first womens fight in the UFC?",
        optionA: "1993",
        optionB: "2003",
        optionC: "2013",
        optionD: "2009",
        correct: "C"
    },     { 
        question: "Who was the first fighter to win UFC titles in 2 different weight classes?",
        optionA: "Conor McGregor",
        optionB: "Randy Couture",
        optionC: "Daniel Cormier",
        optionD: "Amanda Nunes",
        correct: "A"
    },     { 
        question: "Who was the first UFC women's strawweight chamption?",
        optionA: "Ronda Rousey",
        optionB: "Carla Esparza",
        optionC: "Rose Namajunas",
        optionD: "Joanna Jedrzejczyk",
        correct: "B"
    },     { 
        question: "Who has the most finishes in UFC history?",
        optionA: "Anderson Silva",
        optionB: "Jose Aldo",
        optionC: "Donald Cerrone",
        optionD: "Fancis Ngannou",
        correct: "C"
    }, 
];


